[match strikes]
♪ ♪
So, there's this story.
It's-it's probably not true,
but, um, I feel like it
sort of applies
to our situation.
And what situation is that?
You know, uh, you and me,
and, I don't know.
I haven't done this before.
You haven't met girls
on the Internet?
What about you?
Do you... do you
do this often, or...?
Do I fuck guys
on my phone?
No. I mean, there was this one
guy that I met online, but...
it was a long time ago.
Sorry, what was your
name again?
It's, uh, Gary.
Gary with a G.
As opposed to, uh...
And, uh, you are?
I'm Ell.
Like the letter.
Ell with an L.
Give me your hand.
Like that.
Wow. Yeah.
There it is.
So you were going to
tell me a story?
Yeah. Uh, so...
Okay, so there's this
card player in the 1800's
named Canada Bill Jones.
And him and his brother find
a game in the back of this
barber shop in the...
in the French Quarter.
Canada Bill, he's been
playing for... for hours,
and he just, like,
keeps losing.
He's losing and
losing and losing.
Hand after hand,
he just like...
nothing he does is working.
And his brother pulls him
aside and he's like...
Hey, uh, Bill.
You're almost broke,
you need to stop playing.
And Bill was like,
no, no, no, come on.
One more hand,
one more hand.
He doesn't quit, he keeps
playing until finally
George grabs him
and he's like,
Bill! Can't you see
they're cheatin'?
And Canada Bill says...
I knew they were cheating
the second I sat down.
And George asks him,
well, if you knew
the game is rigged,
why the hell
did you play?
And Canada Bill says...
What choice did I have?
It was the only
game in town.
Is this about you and me?
-Well, I mean, no, it's about...
[cellphone buzzing]
-Love or sex or...
-I'm sorry.
The odds are stacked against
us but we keep trying.
Oh, just my friend.
I-I told her to call me
just in case you're,
like, a killer.
I get it.
-Hi.
-I'm not, by the way.
Hi.
No, it's all good.
Mm-hmm.
[chuckles] See you later.
So... do you wanna
get outta here?
Uh...
Yeah. I mean, are you sure?
It's-it's... it's early.
We could, you know,
we could see a movie.
Or they have really good,
um, jalapeño...
[laughs] God. Relax.
It's not that scary.
Right? It's just sex.
Let's go and do it.
Uh...
♪ ♪
♪ [80's style synth music] ♪
It looked nicer
on the website.
I mean, it couldn't
have looked worse.
Yeah. Uh...
This is perfect,
it's like a metaphor.
What does that mean?
Hello?
Uh...
[bell dings]
What do you want?
I have a...
I have a reservation.
[clears throat]
We're closed.
For cleaning.
Oh, looks like you need it.
Sorry, no one said anything
about being closed
when I made
the reservation, so...
[sighs]
Okay. Name?
It's under, uh,
Harry Houdini.
Not my real name.
No shit.
Well, uh, Toby...
can we have a room, please?
This is a scam, right?
Wow.
I've seen this.
They do it all the time.
Lure sad old guys
off the Internet,
make 'em fall in love.
Next thing you know,
your money's gone.
So is she.
Maybe a couple kidneys too.
Happens every day,
doesn't it, sweetheart?
Well, I'm not
as old as I look.
Too old for her.
No, she's 32.
30?
27?
25? You're 25?
Yeah. And?
No. It's good.
You're-you're...
she's a very mature 25.
Well, I'm glad you guys
sorted that out.
Listen.
Girl talk.
What's your deal?
You trying to
piss off Daddy?
Is that it?
You're such a fucking racist.
That's my deal.
[chuckles] Hell.
Just another white trash
redneck asshole.
Okay. All right, let's go.
We're leaving.
-Thank you.
-We're not leaving.
Thank you, good night.
You're gonna rent us
a room, right?
Are you?
Because I'm gonna
call the police.
You're gonna call
the cops on me?
-Hey. Hey, hey.
-Yeah.
No no no no no.
You're gonna call
the cops on me?
She's joking.
She's definitely not joking.
Um... no one is gonna
call the cops
'cause we've all seen what
happens when people try to
weaponize authority. Right?
So, we wouldn't do that.
When they come here,
I bet they're gonna find
all sorts of crazy shit.
So, you wanna try me?
Hundred bucks.
-Okay. Amazing. Great.
-Good!
Now we're talking.
Thank you Toby.
Uh, diplomacy wins again.
Cash only.
I.
I... I don't have cash.
Nobody has cash.
Oh, well, I'm sorry, man.
Someone cut the, uh,
the phone line here,
so you have to find
someplace else.
The gas station.
I saw on the way over.
There's an ATM.
We're going there.
That's, like, two miles.
And then we're coming back.
And you're giving us
that room.
You feel me?
You guys want turndown?
Yes, we do.
Okay. Great.
Come on, I have the map.
You know, it's been
so nice to meet you, but...
I think we should
just call it a night.
Absolutely not.
You heard what I said.
We're going to
the gas station.
We're getting some cash,
and then you, my friend,
are going to town
on all of this.
Right?
Okay. Look, I...
I know why I want this.
Look at you. But...
What are you doing here?
Why me?
Because I wanna have fun.
And you seem nice.
Plus, you're mostly harmless
and I don't know.
For better or worse,
you're what I wanna do.
So... please, let's go.
Two miles is a long walk.
Well, then it's a good thing
that asshole had left
his car keys here.
[car alarm chirps]
We are not taking
this guy's car.
Oh, yes we are.
He's not even gonna notice.
Plus, that guy was a dick.
So, it's only fair.
Here. You drive.
I am not driving
a stolen car.
Um, it's not stealing.
It's borrowing
without permission.
Totally different.
I feel like it's not.
Oh, come on, Gary.
You don't wanna walk
two miles away, do you?
No, of course not.
Look at me.
No one wants that.
Come on then,
live a little.
♪ ♪
For the record.
This is a bad idea.
[scoffs]
Okay.
♪ Share your powers ♪
♪ You stir my soul
and whet my hunger ♪
♪ And weave that spell
that pulls me under, oh ♪
♪ These moonlight desires
haunt me ♪
♪ They want me, they want me ♪
♪ These moonlight desires
haunt me ♪
♪ You're sending,
you're sending ♪
♪ Secret fires burning ♪
Keep the doors locked.
I can take care of myself.
Okay.
[Gary sighs]
Hey. Uh, you...
you got a cash machine?
Yeah, just right
over there.
[groans]
[chuckles]
What the hell
are we doing here?
Hey, my man.
You steal that car?
Um...
Well, 'cause I know that car
belongs to Toby at the motel.
And you're not Toby.
So, I'm thinking maybe
you stole that car,
and maybe I should
call the cops.
No. No no no no.
See, that, uh...
Yeah, no. That car
is Toby's car.
Of course. Um...
We, we... I just...
Toby, uh...
loaned me his car.
Anyway, um... I just came
from the motel,
we're guests,
and Toby lent us the car
and just told us to
come over here and get some...
get some cash.
Oh.
Yeah. Toby's a heck
of a guy, eh?
[door opens]
Yeah, he comes around here
pretty much every night.
Well, except for tonight.
It must be busy, I guess.
Everything cool?
Yeah, yeah.
Everything's cool.
He, uh... he recognized
the car from the motel,
and so I was just
telling him how Toby
let us borrow the car
to get some cash.
Yeah.
Yeah. I mean, he...
he did that, all right?
Hell of a guy.
Yeah, he's also
a total tech wizard.
He actually helped me
set up all these cameras.
Now I catch every face
that comes in here.
Plus the pumps.
4K stereo.
Any punks come in here, try to
start some shit with me,
I take the video,
I send it to the cops,
boom, bust their ass.
All thanks to Toby.
Boom.
Well...
We will have this.
-Sure. Yeah, um...
-Right on.
Uh...
Oh, on card.
Yeah. For sure.
There we are.
-Sign there.
-Of course.
Yeah, maybe, uh, maybe I'll
go visit him after...
after my shift here.
Oh, yeah.
You should, um...
-You should.
-I'll tell him to...
I'll tell him to keep
an eye out for you.
Thanks. Oh, thanks a lot.
Yeah, yeah.
See you later, guys.
[sighs]
Nice people.
We shouldn't have
taken this car.
Relax.
We'll be back
in five minutes.
Plus, what's done is done.
Hey.
You know what?
It was kinda sexy how
you lied back there.
I didn't know you
had it in you.
Yeah, me neither.
[ominous music]
[engine revs]
Oh...
[bell dings]
Maybe he's cleaning the rooms.
[scoffs]
Did that guy look like
a man who cleans anything?
Should we call the company?
[bell dings]
He has to be somewhere.
Okay, let's split up.
You'll go and check
the rooms.
I'll check the car.
We'll find something, right?
Yeah. Yeah.
[bell dings]
Pretty.
Hello?
Uh... is anyone here?
I'm a good person.
I, uh... I collect
action figures.
Stupid.
[laughs] Bingo.
[dial tone]
[phone rings]
[phone ringing]
[screams]
Oh my God. Oh my God.
What is it?
Are you hurt?
[out of breath]
Inside. There's a room.
But, uh, it's, uh...
I think something
bad happened.
Uh... me too.
Is that money?
Where'd you find that?
Oh, fuck! Oh!
I just heard a phone ringing,
so I came and I opened
the trunk and... and then
he was just there.
Was he there
the whole time?
Was I... was I driving around
with a dead guy?
You should ask him.
-We should, uh...
-Yeah.
We should do something.
Right.
What, what...
what are you doing?
What are you doing?
What did you say?
We should do something.
Yeah, I meant, like... we say
a prayer or something.
Not put your bare hands
on a murder weapon.
Fine.
-I'll put it back.
-What?
Put it back?
[flesh squishes]
-Stop that! Oh!
Stop it! Just don't put...
-Stop! Stop doing things.
-There!
Oh! Oh, this is bad.
Oh, this is really,
really, really, really bad.
Wanna see something else?
-Who's this?
-Shit.
You see?
You see this?
That man.
The clerk, Toby.
I don't think
that was Toby.
I think he killed Toby.
That's Toby.
Well, where is...
where is that guy now?
Maybe he left, huh?
Yeah.
Gary?
What do we do?
We need to get outta here.
-Come on. Come on!
-You're kidding.
-Let's go!
-Are you kidding?
We need to get out of here.
[engine revs]
[tires squeal]
What are you doing?
You have to stop.
We have to go back.
No! Okay, we can't go back.
We can never, ever,
ever go back.
Well, we're victims too.
Just call the cops and
tell them what happened.
Call the cops?
Are you paying
attention, okay?
Look, we told the guy
at the gas station
that Toby let us
borrow his car,
and he has us on
freaking video
saying that we were
speaking to the victim.
So, if we call the cops, guess
who their first suspects are?
Us. They're gonna
think we killed him.
But we didn't.
Yeah, but I was
in the room.
I touched his blood.
His blood is on my hand.
And your fingerprints
are on the knife.
And we were in the lobby,
and we have a bag of cash,
and we took the guy's car.
What about the other guy?
What other guy?
We saw him. Do you know
anything about him?
Do you know his name?
We just know his
name isn't Toby.
Does he even exist?
Nobody else saw him.
Where is he?
Well, we can explain
everything, and...
eventually they're gonna
figure it out.
And while they
figure it out, what,
we just wait in jail?
And we wait for this other guy
to come and murder us.
Which he definitely will do,
because we are the only two
people in the whole world who
can pick him out of a lineup.
What are you watching, like,
100 cop shows or something?
Yes. I'm 40 years old. Okay?
-God.
-I watch cop shows.
And I listen to podcasts,
and I go to Costco.
I have a job and
a retirement plan,
and I am gonna lose everything
the second that my face
pops up in the newspaper
next to a dead body.
Newspaper?
Who's even reading
the fucking newspaper anymore?
My wife is.
My wife reads
the newspaper.
What? Stop the car!
Stop the fucking car!
Stop the car!
Ell, wait!
Would you slow down?
Go fuck yourself, Gary.
I never said
I wasn't married.
Is that supposed to
make me feel better?
You... you never said?
Like, what, are you trying
to cover your ass
so she doesn't find out?
Hey, can we talk
about this later?
Why?
We are in serious
trouble right now.
We didn't do anything.
Do you know how many guys
like me who never did anything
end up in prison?
Okay, the truth
does not matter.
Well, then, let's
take him back.
Pretend that it
never happened.
-Walk away.
-But we were there.
Eventually they're gonna
find that gas station.
They're gonna find
that video,
and then they're gonna
come looking for us.
The way I see it,
we have two options.
Option one,
we go to the police.
Maybe I get shot and we
definitely get arrested.
And we spend weeks in jail
trying to prove we're innocent
while the real killer walks
around or comes to kill us.
No, no, I'm not
going to jail.
I cannot go to jail.
I can't.
Great. Same page.
So, option two.
We get rid of the body.
We get rid of the body
and we bury it somewhere
that no one will look,
and then we just...
we cross our fingers
and we just wait, okay?
No body, no crime.
No crime, no reason
to look for us.
And he'll just be some guy who
took off and never came back.
[groans]
Okay. If we, if we, if we do
what you say we should do...
then we can just go home?
-Hmm?
-I don't know.
I mean, no promises,
but I feel like
it's not gonna get
worse than this.
And the money, hmm?
It's yours.
Take it, I don't care.
Give it to charity.
Do whatever you want with it.
How much...
you think is in...
in the bag?
Hmm?
I don't know,
probably 40K.
We'll need some tools.
Yes.
Are you texting right now?
No. I'm searching how to
get rid of a dead body.
I don't think
that's a good idea.
Why not?
Because there's, like,
records of that.
So, what's she like?
Who?
Your wife, asshole.
The woman you're
trying to cheat on.
Can we focus on
staying out of jail?
Come on.
What's her name?
What does she look like?
Does she know you're
a lying piece of shit?
Her name is Alice.
And no, she doesn't know.
See, now we're
getting somewhere.
You're probably one of those
dicks who start off sweet
and then... bam!
The moment she
turns her back,
you're banging
her best friend.
Okay, well, it is
the first time,
and I don't wanna
talk about it.
You don't wanna
talk about it?
-No.
-No?
Whatever you want, buddy.
Did you ever stop
to think that maybe
I didn't want to be
the other woman?
Huh? Maybe I don't like
the idea of helping someone
cheat on his wife.
Did that occur to you?
What is your problem?
I thought young people
don't even believe
in monogamy anymore.
It's all open marriages
and poly triads.
Well, at least I'm not
a fucking narcissist
who tries to rationalize
banging someone else.
Well, you wanna...
you wanna talk about
my loving wife?
Fine. Okay.
Well, she's been
cheating on me.
She's been cheating on me with
some fucking computer hacker
from work for the last
six months like clockwork.
And one day, I followed her
to his house, and I saw
pictures of my wife with
the IT guy's dick like this.
Okay, so... yeah.
I wanted to get even.
I just wanted to feel like
I was in control of something.
Okay?
But you don't
understand that.
You don't understand that
because you don't know
anything about what it's
like to love someone
and then lose that love.
You don't know what it's
like to be lost
and alone and feel helpless.
And I hate how fucking
pathetic I sound
when I say that, but you don't
know anything about pain.
You don't know anything
because you're just
a fucking baby,
and you think you know
everything about everyone
and you don't know shit.
I'll wait for you outside.
[sighs] First date.
Can I get a receipt?
[honks]
What's your problem?
Oh, I, uh...
I'm really sorry
to bother you.
Um, but my, uh...
uh, my car broke down.
I need a ride.
Dude, I can't help you.
Get off the road.
I'm asking nicely.
I don't give a shit.
Oh!
I'm telling you
for the last time,
get outta my face.
I don't wanna
fucking hurt you, man.
Oh, shit.
A big guy. [chuckles]
Do you like the cold?
-The cold?
-Yeah.
The fuck you talking about?
This. You like it?
I can't stand it.
I can't fucking stand it.
Gets in my bones and just...
You know?
Okay, man. That's it.
[knife slashes]
[man groans]
Fucking psycho, man.
Come here.
[grunting]
Shit.
♪ ♪
♪ Love goes ♪
♪ Only to those who believe ♪
♪ But where did our love go? ♪
♪ Close as a heartbeat ♪
♪ But you'll never know ♪
♪ Where did our love go? ♪
♪ Holding it closer ♪
♪ Then letting it go ♪
[indiscernible arguing]
[police siren chirps]
Don't mention the dead body
in the trunk.
Oh, you think?
Everything okay here?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, we're hanging out.
It's all good.
All good in the hood.
You've been drinking
tonight, sir?
No.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah.
But, um, not for...
not for a few hours,
so I'm...
I'm all good.
How, uh...
how are you doing?
How are you guys?
Got some ID on you?
Why do you need my ID?
You want us to
search the car?
We'll be here all night.
No, no. Um...
No, yeah, I mean...
who cares about
due process, right?
Hey.
Get it slowly.
Listen, he hasn't
done anything.
It's just...
it's a blind date.
You can't meet any
women your own age?
They don't like me.
Quite a mess you got
in that car.
[chuckles]
Do you have a kid?
No.
Imagine dragging
a three year old...
around from, like, daycare
to her grandmother,
doing five loads
of laundry,
making meals for the week
so she has something
decent to eat while
you're doing two jobs.
And then having your
little girl being bullied
by a little bitch
with a cell phone.
How often do you get
to clean your car?
Who the hell gives a three
year old a cell phone?
That was exactly
what I said.
Miss.
I'm gonna ask you
a question.
If there's anything
wrong here, you can signal.
-We're... we're fine.
-Sir... don't.
So, if you blink twice,
I'll know what to do.
Just like this.
I'm fine.
Thank you.
All right.
Well, we're gonna go get some
de-icer at the hardware.
[police radio static]
We're gonna need
two units right now.
[Officer] Over. Copy that.
Do you really have a kid?
Yeah, I do.
I didn't know.
I didn't know your
wife cheated on you.
So, I guess we're even.
Okay, let's... let's go.
♪ ♪
Do you wanna talk about it?
I mean, your wife.
Do you--
Not really.
Are you sure?
Because that shit
would mess me up.
And here I am, dumping a body
in the middle of the woods.
Well...
You know, I was,
I was just thinking
that if we're gonna
bury a guy...
we should get to
know one another.
Fine.
How about this kid that
you failed to mention?
Let's talk about that.
What does she have
to do with anything?
You're a mom.
You have a three year
old daughter,
and you're out meeting
some guy for anonymous sex.
That doesn't raise
a few flags?
Don't shame me for
having a night out.
I was gonna be home by 9:30.
Where's her father?
It doesn't matter.
Why are you even
asking me shit?
I just wanted some fun.
And I'm not searching
for a new friend, Gary.
I... you know I don't
want anything.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
You didn't want to know me,
and whatever we came here for,
I didn't wanna
know you either.
Okay, we are just
two people who never
wanna see each other again.
Do you still love your wife?
Yeah.
And that's probably
the worst thing about me.
That's deep enough.
He doesn't really look...
[gasps]
Oh my God.
Oh shit!
What the fuck, Gary?
-No no no!
-No!
No no no!
You said he was dead!
I thought he was.
Okay, why didn't you check
his pulse or something?
Because I'm not
a fucking doctor!
No. No no no no.
That wasn't me.
That was not me.
Me neither.
Ahh... ahh!
[screams]
Oh shit!
We need him back.
Why? What--
Toby!
Slow down!
[Toby screaming]
Toby!
It wasn't us!
Wait wait wait wait.
We just wanna help you.
Wait!
We found you like that.
Toby!
-[groans]
-Ooh!
Oh, no.
Is he dead again?
Hey, buddy.
Uh...
Toby.
It's us again.
Ahh!
Uh, hey.
[Toby groans]
Hey. Hey.
Hey. Yeah.
[groans]
Oh... oh no.
No no no no.
[gags]
[grunts]
-Run run run!
-[Ell screams]
♪ ♪
[screaming]
Ahh!
Shit! Shit! Shit!
[growling]
Drive!
Get us out of here, please.
♪ ♪
♪ So don't play your
girlfriend games with me ♪
I think we lost him.
♪ Stop phoning my house
every evening ♪
♪ Ain't gonna be sliced up
and served for tea ♪
[both scream]
[thud]
[all screaming]
♪ You ain't got me ♪
♪ Like you want me ♪
Stop the car!
[tires screech]
[groaning]
♪ You got ain't me ♪
Did we kill him?
-No.
-[Toby gasping]
I mean, I mean,
probably, but not...
not yet.
I just wanna say
we're so sorry.
We are so, so,
so, so sorry.
And... and that... that is not
an admission of guilt
by the way, you were,
like, pretty much dead,
uh... when we found you.
Uh, Ell actually
told me you were dead.
And, you know, I know
we didn't... we didn't help.
We didn't help things,
obviously, with the... and the..
you know... you know how, just,
like, when you freak out,
stuff kinda just happens,
you know what I mean?
You get it.
And, you know, I guess
not a great time,
Your friend from
the gas station said, um...
said he might stop by.
I don't, um, you know...
What's wrong with you?
You-you have my
condolences, but...
[gurgling]
I think he's trying
to say something.
You have to do
something for me.
We promise.
Anything you want.
Well, no.
Let's... within reason.
Give this to Laura.
Tell Laura...
I still love her.
Hear him?
I think he's really
dead this time.
Okay. Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, he's definitely dead.
Just, uh...
Yep.
Still dead.
Yeah.
Okay, just...
Would you fucking stop that.
Okay. He has...
he has a habit.
[groans]
Okay. Back to the hole.
Didn't you hear him?
Yeah, I heard him
gurgling, and I don't know.
Is that contagious?
I know that's not what
he died from, but...
We made a promise.
We have to find Laura
and give her this.
Fuck me.
Absolutely not.
I can't even believe
we're talking about it.
We have to.
We killed him.
Would you stop saying that?
If anything, we almost
saved his life,
except for the part
where he died.
You ran him over.
Look, someone killed him,
probably that asshole
at the motel,
and stuffed him
in the trunk.
And he would've
died in there
if you hadn't made us
take that car.
But he wasn't dead.
But it doesn't matter.
It's like Schrödinger's cat.
He was both alive and dead
until we came along
and opened the trunk.
You hit him with a car.
He had a knife!
Of course he had a knife!
Somebody stabbed him.
Somebody. That's my point.
Not me and not you.
Okay? So... it's not
our responsibility.
Why is Toby still out there
in the trunk, then?
Because you won't
let us bury him.
-Look.
-Okay.
I know you wanna
do the right thing.
I get it, but this is
not our problem, okay?
We're the victims here.
And... and him. He's...
he's also a victim here.
But... but we count more
'cause we're alive.
Wow.
Do you think this guy is
just gonna forget we exist?
Forget the bag of money
that we stole from him?
We borrowed it
without permission.
And you said you were
Harry Houdini, so...
he will never be
able to find us.
What's the big deal, huh?
The big deal is you wanna
chauffeur around a corpse
to find some girlfriend.
Tell Laura...
I still love her.
I mean, those were
his dying words.
It doesn't matter.
It mattered to me.
It would've mattered to me.
Your... your boyfriend?
My husband.
He was Canadian in Bulgaria,
working on pipelines.
We met, we fell in love.
We moved here.
The next thing I know,
I'm alone with a child
while he's always
traveling for work.
The last time he left, I...
I was angry and I told him
I didn't care if he came back.
He told me he
didn't care either.
And then he...
he didn't.
Come back.
So, we cannot leave Toby
in the fucking woods.
We're gonna find Laura.
We're gonna tell
her the truth.
We're gonna tell her...
that he loved her.
And let her decide.
[sighs] Okay.
How do we find Laura?
I mean, like, where do...
where do we even start?
Easy. We take Toby home.
♪ ♪
This is a terrible idea.
We're breaking
the law right now.
We're doing a favor.
It's fine.
Just be cool.
Come.
What if Laura
isn't even real?
What if she's a cat
or a sex doll.
A sex doll?
She's not a sex doll.
She's a person
and Toby loved her.
Well, where did love get Toby?
Where does it get any of us?
I mean, you don't
have to be so bitter.
Maybe you and your wife
can work things out.
Not to be rude, but I don't
really want marriage advice
from the girl that
I tried to use for sex.
[scoffs]
Wow. I mean, first
of all, I'm a woman.
And second, I was
using you for sex.
What was your plan here?
I don't know.
I mean, the plan was we...
sleep together, and then I...
feel weird, and she finds out,
and then she kicks me out,
and then I don't
have to confront her.
Sounds really mature.
It's not mature.
That's the point.
I'm... I'm done being mature.
If I talk to her
and she'll cry and...
we'll... we'll make up and we'l
fix things for a little bit,
and then eventually we'll
just be right back here.
I'm... too much of
a coward to just leave.
So, I want her
to push me out.
But on my terms.
Would you at least
listen to yourself?
I mean, you just said it.
You met up with
a girl for sex.
You stole a car.
You were going to
bury a dead body
then now look at us.
We're breaking into
someone's house.
Doesn't really sound
like a coward to me.
Crime is one thing.
Love is worse.
Okay.
Why don't you go upstairs?
Maybe you're gonna find
something about Laura
and I can...
I can still look around here.
Let's do that.
[exhales]
Gary!
I found a letter from Laura.
Dear Toby.
This is goodbye.
Oh, shit.
There is no easy way
to say this, so...
I'm just gonna say it.
I did something stupid in
the past and now that past has
caught up with me.
Last year, I got into
some money trouble.
This friend of my brother's
offered to help me out.
Only that friend
turned out to be a...
angry, drug dealing asshole.
And when I couldn't
pay him back,
he told me I had to
work it off.
So I ran, and I moved here,
hoping he'd forget.
And...
and then I met you
and it was perfect.
Until he found me.
And now he says I have to
pay double or I'm dead.
Well, you don't have $40,000.
So, I have to run again.
Toby, if there was
any other way,
if I had the money, if...
if I could stay
here with you.
I can't risk my life.
And...
I won't risk yours.
So, this is goodbye.
I can't tell you
where I'm going.
But wherever I am,
I love you.
Know that I will
always love you.
Toby, you son of a bitch.
Oh, no.
Shit shit shit shit shit!
[glass shatters]
Ell. Quick.
Get up here now!
-What happened?
-The guy!
Whoa!
What is this place?
Quiet! Shh!
Fuck!
How did he find us?
Maybe we're not
who he's looking for.
[grunts]
[man grunting]
Fuck this fucking...
[objects breaking]
[phone rings]
What?
[sighs]
Yeah, okay.
I'll head over there now.
Shit, that was close.
Yeah.
Look at this baby owl.
It's so cute, huh?
[owl hooting]
What the fuck?
-Run.
-What?
Run, Ell!
[yelling]
Fuck!
[chuckles]
Oh, shit!
Shit!
Stop running, you fuck!
[groans]
Wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait.
It's a nice trick, Houdini.
Wait. Okay.
Let's just talk
about this.
Nobody needs to get hurt.
Except the guy you killed.
Nobody... nobody else
needs to get hurt.
Shut the fuck up.
I don't wanna talk.
No no no no no.
I know why you killed him.
He... he put in spy cameras
and he's blackmailing you.
What? What the fuck?
You put in what?
Uh...
-That's not... okay.
-No.
No, that was...
that was just an idea.
What fucking spy camera?
What the fuck do you know?
Nothing! I don't
know anything.
I'm just a guy, okay?
Standing in front of
another guy saying...
please.
Please don't kill me.
Those are your last words.
Wait!
[tires screech]
Get in. Let's go.
♪ ♪
Fuck!
♪ Wild, wild is what I am ♪
♪ Catch me, catch me ♪
That was insane.
He was gonna, like,
smash my brains in
and then all of a sudden,
you came up like, ohh...
Oh my God, ooh!
Ahh, my hip.
That was pretty
brave back there.
You didn't have to save me.
Yeah. You didn't
have to come back.
♪ Round and round
and round we go ♪
I'm hungry.
Are you hungry?
Starving.
[Ell laughs]
♪ ♪
Okay.
So, Laura owes all this
money to the drug dealer.
Yeah.
And then she has
to skip town.
-But, Toby...
-Toby loves her.
Toby just doesn't
wanna lose her.
He wants to save her.
So, he put spy cameras
in the motel
and then starts blackmailing
people for weird shit?
Which gives him a lot of money
with which he can actually
pay Laura's debt.
He schedules a meeting
with the drug dealer.
But obviously his
payoff goes wrong.
-Toby ends up dead...
-Exactly.
And now this other guy,
the drug dealer,
is out there looking
for Laura and the money.
And us.
[chuckles] Oh my God.
Okay, so what do we do?
Nothing's changed.
We still have to find Laura.
We have to hand over
the disk and...
tell her what Toby said.
Ell, come on,
we don't have anything.
You know, we don't
have an address.
We don't have an email.
We don't even have
a phone number.
I think we can just
admit we tried our best,
we looked everywhere we could,
and we just can't find Laura.
There is one place
we didn't look at,
and that's Toby's phone.
You're a genius.
That was not my idea.
I wanted to go home.
♪ ♪
Hey, can I help you, man?
Yeah. I'm, uh, looking
for a couple people.
Came in probably
a few hours back.
Classic car.
Nice one, actually.
Beat to shit.
Yeah. Toby's car.
Yeah, they were nice people.
Right. Toby. Yeah.
They use a credit card?
Uh...
This thing.
I think so...
Yeah? Okay, well, then
I'm gonna need your receipts.
Okay? Also, I'm gonna
need your hard drives.
All of them.
Wait, no, no.
I-I can't do that.
Um... who are you?
[sighs] Who am I?
Do you like the cold?
Do I like the...
The cold.
Do you like it?
Yeah, that's one of the things
I can't wrap my head around.
You know, everybody
in this country
fucking hates the cold.
[chuckles] They hate it.
You know...
I hate it, too.
But I'm not...
I'm not from here.
Maybe you could tell.
And I don't want
to be here anymore.
So, it's super important
that you help me out.
Look, uh... I don't want
any trouble, man.
Well, nobody wants
trouble, Asam.
Just like nobody
wants the cold.
And yet, here we are.
Shivering.
[screams] What the fuck, man?!
Ahh!
Gary Clark.
What a neat guy.
Okay, how do we unlock it?
Well, just point it
and then swipe.
It's easy.
Okay. It's not doing anything.
I mean, do it the right way.
-Turn it!
-Okay. Okay.
How old are you?
I use a passcode.
Look, it's not working.
Unless... does it only
work on living people?
Does the phone
know he's dead?
Well, then make him
look alive.
Make him smile or
something, I don't know.
You make him smile.
Fine.
No, that's not a smile.
Okay. This
feels disrespectful.
Ugh! Forget it.
It's not gonna work.
You know, we have to
find a hacker, right?
Okay, we just find a hacker.
We go to a computer
technician at midnight.
Or do you know a hacker?
I don't, but your wife does.
-No.
-Yes.
Absolutely not.
Absolutely the way.
The only way.
No way.
I don't wanna do that.
You followed her to his house,
so you know where he lives.
No chance.
No way. Uh-uh.
Okay, so you maybe
have a better idea.
I'm listening.
I need you to let me
handle the talking,
because this is kind of
a weird situation
and I don't want
things to get tense.
I mean, isn't he, like,
banging your wife?
Don't you wanna
confront him?
Well, do you want him to
hack the phone or not?
Of course I do.
Okay, well, then we both
need to act like adults,
and I hope you can
handle that.
Don't worry about me
being an adult.
I'm not the one who
looks like a giant baby.
[people cheering]
♪ ♪
♪ Fly forever ♪
♪ Last December ♪
♪ I remember ♪
[crowd chatter]
Hey, how's it going?
Uh, I'm... I'm sorry.
I don't think I know you.
I'm-I'm... I'm Chad.
[high pitched ringing]
Is he okay?
You okay, bud?
-You son of a bitch!
-Whoa whoa whoa!
You home wrecking
piece of shit!
Chill, dude!
Who the fuck
are you people?
I'm Ell, and this is Gary.
You're plowing his wife.
Okay, uh, we need you
to hack this phone.
Wait, wait.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Whose wife?
Oh...
Gary.
Alice said that it was
all over between you two.
She said you were
basically just roommates.
Yeah, well, I guess she
lied to both of us, then.
How'd you find out?
Pictures.
So, yeah, I've seen
your dick and it's weird.
My dick's not weird.
I know it's B, B-plus.
Can we please stay focused?
Where do you fit
into all this?
We met online for sex.
My husband died.
I was working through shit.
So... long story.
Mm-hmm. That's very
interesting, Gary.
You're having an affair too?
Yeah. Except mine is
for a good reason.
Revenge.
Okay. We just need you
to hack this phone.
Can you do that, please?
Look, I can try.
I mean, least I can do
after a home
invasion, right?
Um, this could take
a minute, so...
go enjoy the party.
Drinks on me.
Come on.
Enjoy the party.
What is this fucking
guy talking about?
Here.
Looks like you need one.
Is that her?
I expected her to have
a dick in her mouth.
[laughs] Like, in every
photo of her.
Is that wrong?
Yes.
She told him
we were roommates.
So?
So, she told me
the same thing too,
except I thought it
was a good thing.
You know, I thought
she meant, like...
we're so good together,
we're like roommates.
Stupid.
Come on, this is
not your fault.
You can't stop people
from doing shitty things.
Yeah, but shouldn't
I be enough?
I mean, like...
shouldn't...
Someone should wanna
love me, right?
Um... I'm gonna...
I'll be right back.
Hey, Gary. Wha--
Thank you.
Hey, um...
have you seen Gary?
Pfft.
I've been seeing
Gary's my whole life.
What?
You don't know him.
Yeah. Gary's never
felt worthy, you know?
So, there's no end
to the amount of shit
that he'll take to
convince himself
that he deserves
to be with her.
But this, you know, this only
brings out the worst in her.
Which in return gives him
even more shit to take
until he gets to
this place now.
Tonight, right?
Where any reasonable man
would walk away.
But he can't.
You know, he can't because
he's convinced himself
that if he walks away now,
all that shit that he took...
is for nothing.
He's a good man.
Oh, history's full of
good men doing dumb things
for the wrong reason.
Do you want any of
these edamames?
-Sure.
-Oh...
Whole bowl.
[crowd cheering]
Are you okay?
Yeah. I, um...
I was looking for
the bathroom.
Howdy, strangers.
Got your phone working.
Don't have sex in my bed.
Okay, look, you gotta
keep it hooked up,
but it should work now.
You're welcome.
Anything?
[gasps] Look!
There's Laura.
[call ringing]
Shh.
[Laura] Hello?
Hi. Hi.
Is this Laura?
Who is this?
How'd you get this phone?
My name's Ell and
I'm a friend of Toby's.
Toby never had friends.
We only met tonight, and...
I can tell you
about it in person.
Look, I know you're
in trouble, and I know
he wanted to help you.
He gave me a message
and some money.
So, err... can we...
can we meet, Laura?
There's a restaurant
off Highway 95.
It's called the Night's End.
It's closed for the season,
but go around back.
I'll leave the door
open for you.
Thank you.
I'll be right there.
Okay.
She's not a sex doll.
I told you.
Let's go.
Ell, you can't go.
[scoffs] What is
wrong with you?
I mean, she's literally
waiting for us. Okay?
No. This is...
this is done.
We need to stop this.
We made a promise.
We told Toby we're
gonna find Laura.
We're gonna
give her the disk.
We're gonna tell her
what happened.
She's in on it.
What?
Laura is in on it.
She's scamming him
for the money.
And maybe she
helped kill him,
I don't know,
but it's a con.
She said on the phone,
Toby never had friends.
Had. Past tense.
Okay. I mean, that
doesn't prove anything.
The name of the restaurant
she's at, what is it?
The Night's End.
The Knight's End.
Other kind of knight.
Look, this is
from the motel.
It belongs to
the other Toby.
I mean, we don't know
if you're right.
You think the murderer just
happens to have a matchbook
from the same restaurant?
God, maybe he ate there.
She said it was closed
for the season.
Okay, maybe he followed her.
Or better, maybe Toby
left it in the motel.
He told us everything
at the motel.
The first thing he said
was they find these guys
on the internet, and they
make 'em fall in love,
and then the next thing
you know, she's gone
and so is the money.
Toby loved her.
Yeah, and he probably did,
but she was using him.
$40,000 and she's
the reason he got killed.
We made a promise.
To a dead man.
A dead man that you ran over.
He was Schrödinger's cat!
Oh my God, here comes
the cat again.
-Just... it doesn't matter.
-Okay.
It doesn't matter.
This is all a lie.
Everything is a lie.
They were cheating him
from the start.
You know what?
You really are
a fucking coward.
You are a coward
and that's it.
Just go home!
You wanna go home
to your wife.
You wanna stay there.
You wanna let her treat you
like garbage, right?
Okay. Do it.
I'm not like that.
I'm not gonna let you go.
It's too dangerous.
[laughs] Excuse me.
You won't let me go?
Who the fuck are you?
Hello?
Take the money.
I don't need her money.
He loved her.
I have to tell her, I...
I have to tell her
how he felt.
She needs to know that he...
loved her.
She doesn't care.
Okay.
What do we do about this?
I'll deal with it tomorrow.
I'm too tired now.
Great.
I guess that's it.
You're wrong.
When you said...
that the worst thing about you
is loving your wife.
You're wrong.
It's not.
Even if she doesn't feel it,
it's the best part
of you, and...
You deserve to be happy.
I mean it.
See you around.
No. You won't.
Hey, buddy?
You wanna come back
up to my party?
It's my birthday.
Uh...
I think I'm just
gonna go home.
All right, that's cool.
You wanna hang out
some time?
No, Chad, I don't think so.
Okay. All right.
Take it easy, Gar.
[exhales]
Gar? Is that you?
I tried calling.
Is everything okay?
Uh...
Did I ever tell you
about Canada Bill?
From work? Or...
No. He's, um...
he's a card player
from the 1800's.
Is this another one of
your history things?
Yeah.
So... Canada Bill, he's...
he's in Louisiana,
and he's playing, and...
him and his... him and
his partner George
find a card game in
the back of a barber shop.
And...
you know, hand after hand,
no matter what,
Bill keeps losing.
And after a while
he's almost broke
and George pulls him aside
and he's like...
Hey, um...
Don't you know
they're cheating?
And Bill says, yeah,
I knew they were cheating
the second I sat down.
So, George asks him,
well, if you knew
they were cheating,
why did you stay?
And what did Bill say?
It's the only game in town.
-I'm having an affair.
-You're having an affair.
Jinx! You owe me a Coke.
-Hey.
Did you have fun?
Not exactly.
Sounds like somebody got laid.
Okay.
Go back to sleep.
Hey.
Why are you still awake?
It's time to go
to sleep now.
Mommy's going to
sleep as well.
[voices on TV]
[knock at door]
Hi, Gary.
[thud]
-[Man] Toby?
-[Toby] Yeah.
I brought the money,
it's, uh... it's here.
Hope cash is okay.
Hey, you know what?
Fuck... fuck you!
Hey! Fucking asshole!
[overlapping yelling]
[groaning]
Rise and shine.
Where am I?
Don't worry, Gary,
you're safe.
For now.
You just got caught up in
somebody else's bad day,
that's all.
Where's the girl?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Why don't you cut
the shit, fuckface?
Where's the fucking girl?
I'm so fucking tired.
Gary. Be smart.
We just wanna talk to her and
make sure everything's cool.
We don't wanna hurt you.
I do.
Listen, you help us now,
you and her can go home,
forget tonight ever happened.
But if we have to
go look for her...
I can't promise
what's gonna happen.
Toby thought you were real.
I know. That was the point.
Oh my God.
These guys are like ghosts.
They float around and nobody
notices them except me.
I make them feel
like they matter.
I make them have
someone to care about.
I give them purpose.
And when it's over,
they give me money.
It's a fair trade.
Is that what Toby got,
a fair trade?
Toby...
was a mistake.
All right, either you
tell me where she is,
or I'm gonna throw
you in the trunk,
and I'm gonna go
find her with you.
Your choice.
What do you wanna do?
No.
No, what?
No, as in
fuck you.
And fuck you.
And... and fuck me, I guess.
Because I'm not
telling you shit.
And... and... and frankly,
you are both horrible,
horrible people.
So, kill me or bash my head in
or whatever you're gonna do
because I am done.
I'm done being afraid!
[grunting]
Shit.
Oh, God.
-Oh...
-Shit.
What you doing there, bud?
You trying to break free?
I thought I could
just give it a...
[grunting]
And but... these are...
these are very, very strong.
Yeah.
-Okay.
-Yeah.
Time for the hard way.
Don't make a mess.
[Ell] Laura.
Hello?
I'm looking for Laura.
We talked on the phone.
Ell, get outta here!
Shut the fuck up.
Yeah, come in. We were
just talking about you.
I... I-I didn't know
you had company.
Oh, no, no. It's okay.
Come here.
I have a message from Toby.
Toby's dead.
I know, and I know
how it happened.
I mean, did you ever wonder
how a guy like that
got 40 grand?
He put cameras in a motel.
Started recording people and
blackmailing them for cash.
[chuckles]
Wow.
Couldn't tell my daughter
I was a good person
if I didn't come and
show you this.
-Here.
-Okay.
[video plays]
Hey.
-You Toby?
-Yeah.
Um... I brought the money.
It's, uh... it's here.
Hope cash is okay.
So, that's it, right?
Laura's free?
She can stop running and
we can stay together.
I gotta ask you
something, man.
Why are you doing this?
Because I love her.
You love her?
You don't know shit
about her, man.
Well, I know that
she loves me.
And if you've ever
been in love before,
you know what that means.
Hey, you wanna see
what you know?
Here, take a look at this.
Come here, let me show you
something interesting.
There's your girl.
That's her.
That's who you love.
That's your girl right there.
And you are a fucking mark.
And the sooner you know that,
the better off you'll be.
Hey, you know what?
Fuck... fuck you!
Hey! Fucking asshole!
Fuck me? Fuck you!
[flesh squishes]
[Toby groans]
Oh no no.
No no no no no.
No no. One more thing.
One more thing before you go.
I have enough money to
get the fuck outta here.
This frozen fucking tundra.
But before that...
I'm gonna kill her, man.
Fuck.
God damn it.
Guess it's true
what they say.
No honor among thieves.
[hammer thuds]
[Ell gasps]
What are you doing here?
I told you to go home.
I did.
Ell.
-Ell!
-Hold still.
Shit. Cut faster!
Ell, faster!
I'm trying!
No!
Who else has seen
that fucking tape?
Everyone.
I posted it online and
I sent it to the police.
You're bluffing.
Okay, just please
let us go.
You have the money.
No one needs to get hurt.
No.
You fucking guys.
You could've walked away.
You could've left me alone.
You could've lived happily
ever after for all I care.
But, no.
You had to go and steal
a fucking dead body!
[thud]
We didn't steal it, asshole.
We borrowed it
without permission.
Gary!
Ell, run!
[Ell grunts]
[both groaning]
[groans]
[punches thud]
Gary.
Ell.
Please.
I have a daughter, please.
Stop. Stop.
-I'm sorry.
-Stop.
I'm sorry. I'm...
so sorry.
Hey, let me ask
you a question.
Do you like the cold?
Hmm?
I'm sorry.
[Laura yells]
[groaning]
[gurgling]
Fuck.
It's mine.
Okay, I think
I'm gonna go now.
Okay.
What was that message?
You said Toby had
a message for me.
What was the...
what was the message?
He said that he loved you.
He knew everything
at the end and...
He said that
he still loves you.
Mmm. That's nice.
Thanks.
[exhales]
Oh...
Oh.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It doesn't hurt so bad.
No.
Not so bad.
♪ Here I am ♪
♪ At 6:00 in the morning ♪
♪ Still thinking about you ♪
♪ It's still hard ♪
♪ At 6:00 in the morning ♪
♪ To sleep without you ♪
♪ And I know that it might ♪
♪ Seem too late for love ♪
♪ All I know ♪
♪ I need you now ♪
♪ More than words can say ♪
♪ I've gotta find a way ♪
♪ I need you now ♪
[police siren]
♪ Here I am ♪
♪ I'm looking out my window ♪
♪ I'm dreaming about you ♪
♪ Can't let go ♪
Is there a problem, Officer?
Ma'am, are you okay?
Oh, yeah.
Tired. [chuckles]
Uh... blink twice if
you're in any danger.
Oh, no. I'm good.
♪ Seemed too late for love ♪
Oh, jeez!
We got a dead body in here!
Hands on the wheel where
I can see them now.
-Don't move!
-Dispatch.
We're... we're on Highway 95.
[chuckles] That's Toby.
♪ ♪
♪ I need you now ♪
♪ More than words can say ♪
♪ I've gotta find a way ♪
♪ I need you now ♪
♪ Before I lose my mind ♪
♪ More than words can say ♪
♪ I need you now ♪
♪ I gotta hear you say ♪
♪ Before I lose my mind ♪
♪ I need you now ♪
♪ ♪